Nine hundred and ninety-eight.
Nine hundred and ninety-nine.
One thousand!
Let's break...
...the limit!
Ray, want to go buy some
protein after school?
I'm sorry, but I must refuse!
After school, I'm...
Here you go.
What is this?
The spare key to our club's room.
None of the other club
members can make it today.
I think you'll be there
even before Miss Rebecca.
Understood.
Thank you for taking the trouble
to tell me, Miss Sera.
I-It's no big deal.
Anyway, thanks for doing it.
U-S-A!
Miss Rebecca?
My deepest apologies.
I guess she likes bunnies.
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 4
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Releases His Secret Power!
Um, so...
This is tea made from some plants
grown by the gardening club.
I hope you like it.
Miss Rebecca,
even though it was an accident,
I am terribly sorry for what happened.
Y-You really don't have to say all that.
I just happened to be changing in there
because my gym class ended early.
Usually...
U-Usually... I wear much
more grown-up underwear.
Oh, I see!
That's wonderful!
Yes.
So please forget about what you saw!
Understood!
Jeez!
So, what is this book?
It seems to be more worn than the others.
Oh, that one.
Those are the collective records
of the gardening club.
There is even information in there that
regular illustrated guides don't have.
That's really amazing.
Have you written in it, too?
Yes.
I have specifically added notes about
flowers that were modified by sorcery.
By sorcery?
That's right!
For example, this plant here
is able to use sorcery.
Really?
Plants have the capacity to do that?
They do!
This is particularly common
in carnivorous plants.
Through the process of evolution,
they've begun displaying phenomena
similar to sorcery.
The mysteries of life.
That's right!
Speaking of, your marigolds
also have their own entry.
I'd love to see that.
Is something the matter?
Oh, nothing.
I'm just happy that I can teach
a new member things like this.
But there are other members
in the club, right?
Sure.
I suppose since I'm from one
of the three great houses
people can't help but keep me at a distance.
They're all lovely people,
but when I try to show them something
like this, they politely decline.
I suppose I also find it
difficult to open up.
That's why I am happy that
you're so easy to talk to!
If you don't mind,
then I'd love to continue receiving
lessons like this from you.
Well, I can be a strict teacher.
I sure hope so.
May I borrow this
book to do some studying?
Of course!
That reminds me.
You'll be on the organizational staff
for the Magic Chevalier, correct?
That's right.
I thought I'd go cheer on Amelia.
Amelia is the big favorite
for the rookie bracket.
The daughter of House Rose,
the leader of the three great houses.
Speaking of,
is there nobody from the third
family at this academy?
That's right.
The Algrens have traditionally attended
the Diom Academy of Sorcery.
I see.
That house also has an eldest daughter.
So I think she'll be a
good rival for Amelia.
The Magic Chevalier is upon us.
The academies will soon begin
their preliminary rounds
and select their representatives.
In the rookie bracket,
you will be facing off
against fellow first-years,
meaning that anybody who's
planning to enter is your rival.
The winner is Amelia Rose!
Sir?
Yes?
May I please fight Ray next?
What?
Miss Amelia wants to fight that nobody?!
How dare that withered scum?!
She will crush him, no doubt.
But White is not going to
be one of the partici—
Ray White...
Will you be my opponent?
Professor Arkwright, I have no objections.
And begin!
Not too heavy...
but fast!
You're quite the mystery, Ray.
You're not very skilled when it comes
to sorcery, yet you excel at the sword.
Your skill in actual battle in the
Kafka Forest was amazing, too.
That's why I wanted to
fight you at least once.
I see.
Those words make me happy.
Let's improve together, then.
Yes!
So strong! So beautiful! So exquisite!
I will land a hit!
Oh, this feeling...
A-And the winner is... Amelia Rose!
You really are amazing.
Ray, that last... that last thing.
What was that?
That was just...
Who... Who are you really?
That damn ordinary!
I would've loved to see that!
It was a close fight, huh?
I guess.
You both looked so cool.
But you're really something with the sword.
Where did you learn that?
I have a master.
A master?
Who teaches you sword fighting?
Not just that.
Sword fighting, sorcery,
what kind of person to be...
so all sorts of things.
She's my mentor in everything, basically.
It was pretty brutal, though.
She was that strict?
Yes.
So much so that life here feels like heaven.
You know,
maybe that ordinary is
actually really something.
He was first in the Kafka Forest, too.
I figured they'd naturally win since
Miss Amelia was on their team,
but maybe it was actually because of him?
Ray White.
I hereby challenge you to a duel!
You better not run!
Don't pee yourself!
Or soil yourself another way!
Sure.
I accept.
You think he'll be okay?
I can help him, if it comes to that.
There's a barrier around this entire area.
Is it so nobody hears the sounds?
Mr. Alium, what are the rules for the duel?
Use this.
Needless to say, the use of
sorcery is permitted, as well.
Al?!
Are you serious?
What?
You're using a real sword?
Whoever admits defeat is the loser.
Beyond that...
we need no rules!
Ray White...
I'll kill you myself!
What's wrong?
Come here and fight, ordinary!
Is this just him getting worked up?
Or is it...
There is no way I will lose to you.
If I can compile sorcery...
there is no way I can lose
to a muscle brain like you!
Ray!
I... I...!
I was born to be the heir to House Alium.
House Alium is a noble line.
Even so, we're in the lower
echelons of the middle tier.
A far cry from being notable.
Over this, I had seen my father
humiliated countless times.
So I decided what the purpose
of my life shall be.
I will raise up the name of
House Alium and ensure that we thrive.
I will relentlessly work at it,
and eventually become a grand sorcerer.
Kill...
Kill Ray White!
Is dodging all you can do?!
If it's just a little...
What?!
He cut the spell?!
Mr. Alium, let me teach
you how big our world is.
Shut up!
Ray!
Back!
Damn it! Damn it, damn it, damn it!
Stop!
What is going on?!
Why won't any of them hit?!
Y-You!
You must actually be a noble!
You're some hidden bastard of
one of the three great houses!
Aren't you?!
I was definitely born an ordinary.
And yet, despite my birth,
I can use sorcery and
I can also fight like this.
Mr. Alium, I understand that
heritage is very important to you,
but that doesn't mean
you're a great sorcerer.
Damn it!
Then eat this!
Hey, Al!
Isn't that an Extensive?!
Febris Draco!
Ray!
I...
What on earth am I...
Ray, you're...
You have to tell us now.
Who are you?
I'm...
This is...
Spectacular.
It really was spectacular.
That is youth for you.
But you will now all become
living sacrifices.
But do not despair.
You will be contributing to the
development of a magnificent sorcery.
Is that not something to be proud of?
Is it not?
Hmm?
Ray White?
Professor Gray?!
Such an exciting situation!
It really makes the heart sing.
R-Ray!
I'll explain myself when this is over.
No more secrets.
But please wait for just a little longer.
It looks like I have no choice
but to fight Professor Gray.
You are obviously no average person.
Neither are you.
And now I understand.
Oh?
Share your thoughts, White.
You belong to Eugenics.
Your aim is to get the students' engrams.
The brains of sorcerers.
I'm sure those expelled students you
alluded to are also a part of this.
You are correct, Ray White.
I don't dislike sharp people.
And now I've become
interested in your engram.
You were trying to abduct students in
the Kafka Forest during that exercise.
That monster that had no
business being there...
You were controlling it.
Correct again.
Truly impressive.
That exercise is a yearly godsend.
It's so easy to excuse that another
student disappeared from the academy.
And then, oh, how I mourn them!
The tragedy's heroine:
"No, why did it have to be my students?!"
Something like that.
You're the one who
incited Mr. Alium, as well.
What an idiot.
Only his pride is big enough to measure.
The rest of him is pathetic trash.
But in the end, he was a convenient stall
for time while I erected this powerful barrier.
I got a promising crop of
students in one fell swoop.
With this many brains,
my standing in Eugenics will rise, as well!
So everything you told
me was a complete lie.
Obviously.
You had caught my eye.
I always talk to students privately
when I'm interested in them.
As the considerate and
compassionate teacher.
So, how did I do?
I played the part well, don't you agree?
Please be prepared to lose an
arm or two, Professor Gray.
What? You're still calling me "Professor"?
All right, Ray White.
You truly are interesting.
I'll keep you alive while I study
that engram in your brain.
Whoa!
You're a sorcerer who has specialized
in close-quarters combat, right?
And despite being an ordinary,
you seem to have an abnormally
high capacity for prima materia.
But as long as you can't get near me,
there is nothing you can do!
Fire Snake!
Now what are you going to do, Ray White?
Watching you just run away isn't amusing.
So then, what about this?
I'll take you all down at once!
However, once the time comes,
you have to make that call.
After all, I did pass the mantle of...
Chronos Lock, release!
What is this?!
What's happening?
I'm sorry, Master...
But I must do this to protect everyone.
Icicle Blades!
Blades... of ice?!
This can't be!
An I-Iceblade?!
They said the Iceblade Sorcerer
disappeared in the Far East War!
That's true.
But the Iceblade Sorcerer
title had been passed on.
To a certain boy...
This can't be, this can't be,
this can't be!
This can't be happening!
Stop spewing... lies!
So what if you have iceblades?!
Even if you are one of the seven grand
sorcerors, you can't block this!
Causality Draco!
Antimaterial Code, activate.
It disappeared?
How?
Professor Gray,
why don't I show you the true
nature of the Iceblade Sorcerer?
What are you saying?
What the hell are you?
Stay back! Stay back!
Frame Lock.
That hurts!
Are you really...
Are you really that Iceblade?
That's right.
I am the Iceblade Sorcerer.
S-Stop!
W-W-W-W-Wait!
Okay, don't say another word.
Please just calm down.
Why don't I, I mean, may I
introduce you to Eugenics?
Yeah, that's a great idea!
I'm sure they'd make you one of their leaders!
So please, let me go!
My research to unveil
the truth cannot end here!
Please, I beg of you!
You idiot!
What?
What's wrong?
Is that it?
You monster...
Is that all, Professor Gray?
I accept it.
Even as a platinum, I can't
compete with grands.
But then the strongest of
the seven grand sorcerers?
I just can't win.
So what will you do with that?
You going to kill me with that iceblade?
No.
Your punishment will fit the crime.
You're going to capture me alive?
I see.
So that's how it's going to be.
Looks like I'm gonna have to go all out, then!
Dark Triad System!
Activate!
You forced me to use this...
The result of all my research so far!
Now, you better let me
have some fun, Iceblade!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
Hello, this is the preview
of the next episode of
The Iceblade Sorcerer Shall Rule the World.
Ray is wielding the emblematic iceblade.
However, that is actually a double-edged
sword that ravages his body.
"The Boy Who Became the
World's Strongest Sorcerer
Has an Unexpected Meeting
on the Battlefield".
Episode 5
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Has an Unexpected Meeting on the Battlefield
This has been Rebecca Bradley.